[
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 16 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "2 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "57 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 3 environmental risks in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2022 is 0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2022 is 67.77"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2022 is 24.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 16 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "2 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "57 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 3 environmental risks in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2022 is 0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2022 is 67.77"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2022 is 24.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 16 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "2 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "57 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 3 environmental risks in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2022 is 0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2022 is 67.77"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2022 is 24.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 16 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "2 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "57 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 3 environmental risks in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2022 is 0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2022 is 67.77"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2022 is 24.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 16 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "2 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "57 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 3 environmental risks in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2022 is 0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2022 is 67.77"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2022 is 24.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 16 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "2 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "57 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 3 environmental risks in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2022 is 0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2022 is 67.77"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2022 is 24.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 16 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "2 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "57 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 3 environmental risks in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2022 is 0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2022 is 67.77"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2022 is 24.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 16 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "2 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "57 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 3 environmental risks in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2022."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2022 is 0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2022 is 67.77"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2022 is 14.28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2022?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2022 is 24.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.36"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 1.2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.48"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 1.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 1.8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.72"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 2.07"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.83"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 2.37"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.95"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 2.67"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 1.07"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 1 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "1 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.99"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 1 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "1 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.99"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 1 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "1 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 0.99"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 2 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "2 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 1.99"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 3 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "3 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 2.98"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.89"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 3 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "3 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2021 is 2.98"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2021 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2021?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2021 is 0.89"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2020?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2020?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2020?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2020 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2020 is 0.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2020 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2020 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2020 is 0.12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of environmental labels Orange received in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of social labels Orange received in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the total number of governance labels Orange received in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 0 environmental labels in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in environmental performance for Orange in 2020?",
        "answer": "0 of the environmental labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in social performance for Orange in 2020?",
        "answer": "0 of the social labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many labels indicate opportunities for improvement in governance performance for Orange in 2020?",
        "answer": "0 of the governance labels indicate opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you provide the breakdown of environmental risks identified for Orange in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange faced 0 environmental risks in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2020 is 0.0."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what areas could Orange potentially improve its environmental performance based on the provided data in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange could potentially improve in areas related to reducing environmental risks and capitalizing on more opportunities for improvement."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many social labels did Orange receive in 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange received a total of 69 social labels in 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total governance score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total governance score for 2020 is 0.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total social score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total social score for 2020 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total environmental score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total environmental score for 2020 is 0.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Orange's total ESG score for 2020?",
        "answer": "Orange's total ESG score for 2020 is 0.12"
    }
]